usawallpaper.com 2017-02-28

# Privacy Policy

Your Privacy and Security is our Top Priority

At Steve’s we want you to have the best shopping experience possible. And while it is necessary for us to collect personal information that you provide us, we respect and protect your right to privacy. We allow our customer to use their wish list and complete a sale without ever having to register. If you are not comfortable completing a purchase on-line you are always able to place your order over the telephone or mail in your order. The following is Steve’s policy regarding your privacy and the security of your personal information. 

  * Steve’s uses Verisign secure socket layer (SSL) technology to encrypt your personal information and payment information when you place an order. 
  * Steve’s uses your personal information to fulfill your order, to contact you if you have questions about your order and to support your use of Steve’s website. 
  * With your permission, we may use your e-mail address to notify you about special promotions and services. 
  * Steve’s may use non-personally identifiable aggregated data in order to better understand how our site is being use and to enhance the buyer experience of all visitors to our site. 
  * You are always able to review and edit your registration information from our site at any time. 
  * Our site is intended for use by the general public that are 18 years of age or older. 

How Your Information is Protected

Steve’s is committed to protecting all of your personal information that you supply us. Steve’s follows reasonable technical and management practices to aid in protecting the security, confidentiality and integrity of the data stored on our systems. Our site uses Verisign secure socket layer (SSL) technology to encrypt your personal information and credit card information when you place an order. This provides for the secure transmission of the information from your computer to our servers. Steve’s does a thorough background check on all of its employees and only employees that need access to your information in order to perform their jobs are allowed such access. All Steve’s employees are informed about their responsibility to protect our customers privacy and we give them clear guidelines for adhering to our own business ethics standards and confidentiality policies. Any employees who violate our privacy and/or security policies will be subject to disciplinary action, and if the violation warrants it they will be terminated and may be charge with civil and or criminal prosecution.

Information That We Collect

Steve’s keeps track of information in order to provide you with a more enjoyable, convenient shopping experience. We allow our customer to use their wish list and complete a sale without ever having to register. If you decide to register with us you will need to provide us with an e-mail address and password so that we can provide you with access to your account. If you are not comfortable completing a purchase on-line you are always able to place your order over the telephone or mail in your order. If you decide to complete your order on-line Steve’s will ask you for your name, phone number, e-mail address, billing and shipping addresses and credit card information (you always have the ability to complete your order on-line and then call in or fax in your payment information). Your information will only be shared with those that need access to such information and only the information that they need will be shared (i.e. credit card processing company, the distribution center that is shipping your order and the shipping company that will deliver your order, etc…). We may use your e-mail address and phone number to contact you regarding any questions we have regarding your order as well as to update you on the status of your order. And if you gave us permission we will use your e-mail address to notify you of special promotions and new services. E-mails are only sent to people that have either purchased from us or have requested that they receive such e-mails. At any time, you may stop receiving e-mails by opting out from receiving such e-mails. Logging in to Steve’s doesn’t obligate you in any way or manner to stevesblinds.com. 

The Scoop on Cookies

Cookies assist our customers with having a more enjoyable, convenient shopping experience. A “cookie” is a small file that is stored by your web browser on your computer’s hard drive. Cookies allow us to recognize who you are when you arrive at our site. When you arrive at our site an anonymous identification number that is stored on our secured servers is associated with your computer. We match those up with any personal information that you provided us and that is how we can recognize who you are. At no time is your personally identifiable information (name, street, address, and payment information) stored within a cookie.

Accepting cookies through your web browser is your personal choice. You can still shop from stevesblinds.com even if you set your browser to disable cookies. However, if you choose to do so, we may not be able to provide you with as exceptional a shopping experience as one that is specifically tailored to your needs.

Changes in Policy

Steve’s reserves the right to change the terms of use and this Privacy Policy, at any time. We will post any changes so that you are always aware of our policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Policy applies to all information that we have about you and your account.
